{
    "subject": "resource/Giallo",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Italian_films_by_genre",
    "human_readable": "Giallo is about Italian films by genre.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8613096475601196,
            "question": "What type of film genre is Giallo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7142125368118286,
            "question": "How has the Giallo genre influenced other film genres?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7000151872634888,
            "question": "What is the subject of Giallo films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5889518857002258,
            "question": "Which country's films are classified as Giallo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5142641067504883,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of Giallo films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49889642000198364,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about Giallo films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49795252084732056,
            "question": "When did the Giallo genre become popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4303915798664093,
            "question": "Who are some famous directors of Giallo films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4079936146736145,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of a Giallo film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40693822503089905,
            "question": "What is the historical context surrounding Giallo films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giallo is about Italian films by genre.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7496_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give me an example of a Giallo film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7496_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous directors of Giallo films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7496_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the Giallo genre become popular?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7496_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7496_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Giallo is about Italian films by genre.\" The texts discuss the characteristics and history of the giallo film genre, its key figures (such as Dario Argento and Mario Bava), and how it has influenced other filmmakers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}